// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "If you were awarded a project, you will start work:",
    answer: "b. After the approval of the authorities",
    options: [
      "a. One week before the approval of the authorities",
      "b. After the approval of the authorities",
      "c. One day before the approval of the authorities",
    
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Project Scope Management:",
    answer: "d. All of the above",
    options: [
      "a. Define scope and control scope",
      "b. Executing scope and verify scope",
      "c. Closing process and Create work breakdown structure",
      "d. All of the above",
      "e. Only A & B",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Scope Management starts with is:",
    answer: "a. To identify the client requirements",
    options: [
      "a. To identify the client requirements",
      "b. Meet the team",
      "c. Review strategic plan",
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Final as built drawings for what purpose",
    answer: "a. To keep record for later maintenance",
    options: [
      "a. To keep record for later maintenance",
      "b. To give more work to architect",
      "c. To be used for further renovation",
    
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Control department work starts",
    answer: "a. From the beginning of the project",
    options: [
      "a. From the beginning of the project",
      "b. During construction",
      "c. After construction",
     
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
    question: "Project management is ideally suited except",
    answer: "e. Repeatability",
    options: [
      "a. Accountability",
      "b. Flexibility",
      "c. Innovation",
      "d. Speed",
      "e. Repeatability",
     
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
      question: "A critical path is the ----------------------in the project management:",
      answer: "a. longest",
      options: [
        "a. longest",
        "b. shortest",
        "c. none",
        
       
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
        question: "The forward pass review of the project management will indicate the following:",
        answer: "c. Critical path (longest path)",
        options: [
          "a. The earliest start of the task",
          "b. The earliest finish of the task",
          "c. Critical path (longest path)",
          "d. Only A & B",
          "e. All of the above",
          
         
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
          question: "The back pass review of the project will indicate the following:",
          answer: "d. Only A & C",
          options: [
            "a. The latest start of the task.",
            "b. The earliest finish of the task.",
            "c. The critical path.",
            "d. Only A & C",
            "e. All of the above.",
            
           
          ]
        },
        {
          numb: 10,
            question: "Intersecting point for WBS and OBS",
            answer: "a. Cost account",
            options: [
              "a. Cost account",
              "b. Intersect matrix",
              "c. Project matrix",
              "d. None of above",
            
              
             
            ]
          },
          {
            numb: 11,
              question: "For operation and designed auto mobile factory",
              answer: "a. Mechanical Engineer",
              options: [
                "a. Mechanical Engineer",
                "b. Civil Engineer",
                "c. Chemical Engineer",
                "d. Petroleum Engineer",
            
                
               
              ]
            },
            {
              numb: 12,
                question: "Which of the following discipline is most suitable for doing a natural gas pipeline work?",
                answer: "a. Mechanical Engg",
                options: [
                  "a. Mechanical Engg",
                  "b. Petroleum Engg",
                  "c. Chemical Engg",
                  "d. Civil Engg",
                  
                  
                 
                ]
              },
              {
                numb: 13,
                  question: "Gypsum board at residence and industrial building used except",
                  answer: "c. Recyclability",
                  options: [
                    "a. Low cost",
                    "b. Ease of installation",
                    "c. Recyclability",
                    
                    
                   
                  ]
                },
                {
                  numb: 14,
                    question: "Stress defined:",
                    answer: "d. None of above",
                    options: [
                      "a. Strain time force",
                      "b. Mass divide volume",
                      "c. Pressure time length",
                      "d. None of above",
                     
                      
                     
                    ]
                  },
                  {
                    numb: 15,
                      question: "Which one of the following is suitable in engineering manner? -Decision shall be based on reason than situation-.",
                      answer: "d. Honesty",
                      options: [
                        "a. Quantity Thinking.",
                        "b. b. Logical Thinking.",
                        "c. Interpersonal Skills.",
                        "d. Honesty",
                        
                        
                       
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      numb: 16,
                        question: "What is the last of estimation for project",
                        answer: "a. Estimation",
                        options: [
                          "a. Estimation",
                          "b. Assembly schedule",
                          
                          
                         
                        ]
                      },
                      {
                        numb: 17,
                          question: "What is QSAS?",
                          answer: "a. Qatar Sustainability Assessment System",
                          options: [
                            "a. Qatar Sustainability Assessment System",
                            "b. Assessment System Qatar Sustainability",
                            "c. Qatar System Assessment ",
                           
                            
                           
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          numb: 18,
                            question: "An activity in a project network can be represented by which of the following?",
                            answer: "d. All of the above",
                            options: [
                              "a. Arrow ",
                              "b. Line",
                              "c. Node",
                              "d. All of the above",
                              
                              
                             
                            ]
                          },
                          {
                            numb: 19,
                              question: "Before starting work at site, the major factor has to be checked is?",
                              answer: "d. Approval from MMUP / Civil / Defence etc.",
                              options: [
                                "a. Access to site (EFE) ",
                                "b. Storage of Water, tools & equipments",
                                "c. Safety",
                                "d. Approval from MMUP / Civil / Defence etc.",
                                "e. All of the above",
                               
                                
                               
                              ]
                            },
                            {
                              numb: 20,
                                question: "Software programming flow:",
                                answer: "a. Plan, Do, Check, Act",
                                options: [
                                  "a. Plan, Do, Check, Act",
                                  "b. Plan, Do, Act, Check",
                                  "c. Plan, Act, Do, Check",
                                 
                                  
                                 
                                ]
                              },
                              {
                                numb: 21,
                                  question: "First step of Scope planning starts with:",
                                  answer: "c. Objectives and requirements to satisfy customer",
                                  options: [
                                    "a. Budgeting",
                                    "b. Current earning estimation",
                                    "c. Objectives and requirements to satisfy customer",
                                  
                                    
                                   
                                  ]
                                },
                                {
                                  numb: 22,
                                    question: "In network which point getting more inward flow:",
                                    answer: "d. Merging point",
                                    options: [
                                      "a. Float",
                                      "b. Critical path",
                                      "c. Slack",
                                      "d. Merging point",

                                    
                                      
                                     
                                    ]
                                  },
                                  {
                                    numb: 23,
                                      question: "What is the least level of WBS:",
                                      answer: "c. Work package",
                                      options: [
                                        "a. Deliverable",
                                        "b. Cost",
                                        "c. Work package",
                                        "d. Lowest sub deliverable",
                                      
                                        
                                       
                                      ]
                                    },
                                   
                                      {
                                        numb: 24,
                                          question: "The best place to build an exhibition and convention center:",
                                          answer: "b.in satellite place far from Urban",
                                          options: [
                                            "a. near the Airport",
                                            "b.in satellite place far from Urban",
                                            
                                          
                                            
                                           
                                          ]
                                        },
                                        {
                                          numb: 25,
                                            question: "What do we call Synchronous motor working on a lead power factor at no lead?",
                                            answer: "a. Synchronous condenser",
                                            options: [
                                              "a. Synchronous condenser",
                                              "b. Reluctance motor",
                                              
                                            
                                              
                                             
                                            ]
                                          },
                                        {
                                          numb: 26,
                                            question: "A Synchronous motor working with No-lead can be used as:",
                                            answer: "a. Synchronous condenser",
                                            options: [
                                              "a. Synchronous condenser",
                                              "b. Induction motor",
                                              "c. Induction generator",
                                              
                                            
                                              
                                             
                                            ]
                                          },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];